var triviaQuestions = [
  {
    question: '1. What is gluten?',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'a protein comprised of two molecules, glutenin and gliadin',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 2',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 3',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 4',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 5',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 6',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 7',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 8',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 9',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 10',
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'A',
      b: 'B',
      c: 'C'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b'
  }
]

//  answerChoices in array:
// var triviaQuestions = [
//   {
//     question: 'Question 1',
//     answerChoices: ['A', 'B', 'C'],
//     correctAnswer: 'b'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 2',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'b'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 3',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'c'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 4',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'a'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 5',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'a'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 6',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'b'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 7',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'a'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 8',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'c'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 9',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'a'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Question 10',
//     answerChoices: {
//       a: 'A',
//       b: 'B',
//       c: 'C'
//     },
//     correctAnswer: 'b'
//   }
// ]
